

YEŞİM AKAR HOZMAN

FRONT-FND DEVELOPER



yesimhozman@gmail.com





EDUCATION

Bogaziçi University Educational Technology Master's Program 10/2020-06/2023 GPA: 3.65

Re:Coded & Flatiron School Front-End Development Bootcamp 04/2021-09/2021

Bogaziçi University Department of Mathematics Education **BA** Degree 2015-2020 GPA: 3.01

SKILLS

- Web Design (Html5, CSS3, SCSS, Bootstrap)
- JavaScript
- React.is
- Symfony, PHP, Twig
- Figma

LANGUAGES

- English C1
- French A7

HOBBIES

- Sculpture
 - exhibition of "Çizgiden Heykele" at Kadıköy Karikatür Evi 2019
- Camping
- Travel

ABOUT ME

I am a front-end developer based in Turkey. I graduated from the mathematics education department at Boğaziçi University. After that, I started my master's degree in Educational Technology there. I formerly worked as a middle school mathematics teacher. I completed the front-end web development bootcamp from Re:Coded. Nowadays, I create e-commerce websites with Shopware 6 and practice Javascript frameworks.

Check my portfolio

EXPERIENCES

Front End Developer

Next-Gen Solution & Innovation 07/2021-10/2022

- Experience building Shopware e-commerce backends
- Developing themes and managing plugins on Shopware 6
- Using Twig, Scss, Bootstrap, Javascript & jQuery to develop ecommerce websites.
- Using Git for version control.
- Familiar with Vue.js & React.
- Knowledge of UX/UI Design Principles.
- Experience working in a scrum process.
- Experience in agile project management.
- Experience in different component libraries (MaterialUI, React Bootstrap, React Router)

Mathematics Teacher

Istanbul Kampus Schools 08/2020-07/2021

Project Member

EKIP Social Cooperative Project ekiplatformu.com 03/2020-08/2020

CERTIFICATES

- Certificate of Completion Front-End Web Development Bootcamp 2021/ Re-Coded & Flatiron School
- Front End Development Libraries/ FreeCodeCamp
- Boğaziçi University Fine Art Certificate 2020
- Oxford Leadership SML Completion 2020
- Certificate of Europass 2018/ Erasmus+ Youth Exchange Project -Spain